Office of the President Jill Ker Conway Files, 1974-1985
Smith College Archives
- SERIES XII. FACULTY AND STAFF
  - Faculty Salaries
    - -General 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - -General 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - -General 1984-1985, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - -Reports 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Spouses 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Women-Equal Opportunity Employment 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fellowships
    - -Mendenhall Fellowship 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -National Humanities Institute Fellows Program 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - -Picker Fellowship 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Individuals
    - -A-C ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -Ainsworth, Dorothy 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - -Banerjee, Maria 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - -Berkman, Leonard 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - -Berzoff, Joan 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - -Betlyon, Stephanie 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - -Bloom, Peter 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - -Bourque, Susan 1977, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - -Butler, Johnnella 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - -Cassidy, Phyllis 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - -Chase, Mary Ellen 1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - -Connolly, John 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - -D-L ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - -Day, Alice 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - -Donfried, Karl 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - -Duckett, Eleanor Shipley 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - -Duke, John 1975-1976, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - -Dunn, Esther Cloudman 1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - -Ellis, Frank 1978-1984 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - -Ellis, Robert 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - -Fowlkes, Martha 1978-1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - -Gabel, Katherine 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - -Goldberg, Maier 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - -Harward, Vernon 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - -Hiatt, Iva Dee 1977, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - -Higgins, Jean 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - -Hopkins, Elizabeth 1983-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - -Horowitz, Helen 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - -Houser, Caroline 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -Koffka, Elizabeth 1978-1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -Koffka, Kurt 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -Lander, Yechiael 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - -Leland, Marine 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - -Leland, Marine-Memorial Funds 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - -M-O ca. 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - -Morris, Cynthia Taft 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - -Morris-Hale, Walter 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - -Nenner, Howard 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - -Notestein, Ada Comstock 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - -Offner, Elliot 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - -P-R ca. 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - -Pinto, Paul 1978-1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - -Quesnell, Quentin 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - -Robinson, Donald 1978-1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - -Rose, Peter 1976-1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - -Rothman, Stanley 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - -S-V ca. 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - -Scales, Laura 1979-1981, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - -Schalk, Marshall 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - -Schuster, Marilyn 1980, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - -Senechal, Marjorie 1976-1985, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - -Spelman, Elizabeth 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - -Soffer, Milton 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - -Talbot, Charles 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - -Unno, Ty 1979-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - -Van Dyne, Susan (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - -Von Klemperer, Elizabeth 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - -Von Klemperer, Klemens 1975, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - -W-Z ca. 1975-1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - -Wood, Ruth Goulding 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - -Zimbalist, Andrew 1975-1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - OBND (Out But Not Down) Club 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Orientation Mailings for New Faculty and Staff 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Physical Fitness Programs 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Retirement Policies 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Early Retirement Program Study Group
  - Secretary of the Faculty 1976-1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Sexual Discrimination (Box 4)
  - Sexual Harassment (Box 4, Folder 13)
    See Administrative Issues-Sexual Harassment
  - Tuition Grants 1976-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Workshops
    - -General 1976-1984 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - -Advanced Management for Women 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - -Lilly Endowment Workshop on the Liberal Arts 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - -Stanford's Organization and Management of Post-Secondary… 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Women and Social Change Project
    - -General 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - -General 1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - -General 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -General 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -General 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - -General 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - -General 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - -General Foundation Reports 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - -Mellon Foundation Proposal 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - -Mellon Foundation Proposal Mar 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - -Mellon Foundation Report 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - -Mellon Foundation Report 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - -Mellon Foundation Report 1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - -Monticello Foundation Proposal 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - -National Endowment for the Humanities Proposal 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - -Women and Biography Workshop 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- SERIES XIII. GRADUATE WORK
  The Graduate Work series includes correspondence, newspaper clippings, and reports regarding the evolution and operation of several graduate studies programs at the college. There are records documenting general aspects of graduate education, as well as specific programs of study, such as the American Studies Diploma Program, teacher training at the Clarke School for the Deaf, the Smith-Northampton Summer School, and the School of Social Work.
  Useful information may also be found in the Committees and Boards series on the Committee on Graduate Study.
  - General 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Studies Diploma Program 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Studies Diploma Program 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Education and Child Study
    - -Clarke School Teacher Training 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      See also Series IV. Admin Issues-Town & Gown Relations-Clarke School for the Deaf
    - -Smith-Northampton Summer School
      - -Annual Reports 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - -General 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - -Evaluation Report 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - School for Social Work
    - -General 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -General 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - -General 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - -General 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - -General 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - -General Jan-Feb 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - -General Mar-Dec 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - -General 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - -General 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - -General 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - -Accreditation 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -Ad-hoc Committee on Governance 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - -Commencement 1976-1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -Day-Garrett Award 1978-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -"Faculty Development…" Project 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - -Human Services Management Program 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - -Jill Ker Conway Award 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - -Mission Statement 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - -Oral History Project 1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - -"Report on a Study of Organization" 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - -Research and Development Center 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - -Student Organization 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - -Women in Prison Project 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Smith Management Program
    - -General 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -General Jan-Jul 1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -General Aug 1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -General Sep 1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - -General Oct 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - -General Nov-Dec 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - -General Jan 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - -General Feb-Mar 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - -General Apr 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - -General May 1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - -General Jun-Aug 1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - -General Sep-Dec 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - -General Jan-Mar 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - -General Apr-Jun 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - -General Jul-Dec 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - -General Jan-Jun 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - -General Jul-Dec 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - -General Jan-Jun 1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - -General Jul-Dec 1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -General Jan-Jun 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -General Jul-Dec 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - -General 1985, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - -Career Development Manual 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - -Feasibility Study 1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - -FIPSE Grant Application 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- SERIES XIV. INTERCOLLEGIATE ASSOCIATIONS
  There are six intercollegiate associations included in this series: Five Colleges, Inc., Seven Sisters, Society Organized Against Racism, Ten Universities Group, Twelve-College Exchange, and Women's College Coalition.
  Five Colleges: The Five Colleges material includes correspondence, reports and newspaper clippings tracing the evolution of cooperative relations between Smith College, Mount Holyoke College, Hampshire College, Amherst College, and the University of Massachusetts at Amherst.
  Seven Sisters: The records of the Seven Sisters (also known as the Seven Colleges) include correspondence, reports and newspaper clippings documenting relations between seven of the most important historically women-only colleges in the Eastern United States: Barnard, Bryn Mawr, Mount Holyoke, Radcliffe, Smith, Vassar, and Wellesley.
  Society Organized Against Racism (SOAR): The SOAR records include correspondence and reports documenting the founding and early activity of the organization. SOAR, founded in 1982, is a consortium of New England colleges and universities working to improve the racial climate in academic institutions.
  Ten Universities Group: The Ten Universities Group file includes the records of a July 1980 conference on issues related to faculty and tenure. The Ten Universities were the California Institute of Technology, Carnegie Mellon University, Case Western Reserve University, Dartmouth College, Duke University, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Princeton University, Rochester University, Vanderbilt University, and Washington University.
  Twelve-College Exchange: The Twelve-College Exchange files include records of the student exchange program begun in 1968 which eventually included the following institutions: Smith, Amherst, Bowdoin, Connecticut, Dartmouth, Mount Holyoke, Trinity, Vassar, Wellesley, Wesleyan, Wheaton, and Williams. The program had a publicly stated purpose of expanding the collegiate experience for the students, but privately was initiated as an experiment in coeducation for several traditionally single-sex institutions.
  Women's College Coalition: The Women's College Coalition was founded in 1972 under the auspices of the Association of American Colleges. It includes more than seventy two- and four-year colleges. The material in this collection includes correspondence, reports and announcements of the organization's events and projects.
  - Five Colleges
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -General 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -General 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - -Coordinator 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - -Directors Meetings 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - -Directors Meetings 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - -Directors Meetings 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - -Directors Meetings 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - -Directors Meetings 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - -Directors Meetings 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - -Directors Meetings 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - -Directors Meetings 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - -Directors Meetings 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - -Directors Meetings 1985, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - -"Glancing Backward:Twenty-Five Years of Cooperation" 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -Academic Departments and Programs
      - -General 1975 -1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - -Afro-American Studies 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - -Canadian Studies 1979-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Special Projects-Canadian Studies
      - -Dance Program 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - -Dance Program 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - -Dance Program 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - -Early Music
        - -General 1978-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - -Evaluation Report 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - -East Asian Studies 1977-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - -Foreign Languages 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - -History of Science 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - -Judaic and Slavic Studies 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - -Latin American Studies 1977-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - -Linguistics 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - -Mathematics 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - -Medieval Civilization, Institute on the Teaching of 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - -New England Studies 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - -Peace and World Security Studies 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
        See also Series III. Academic Programs-Peace & War Studies
      - -Peace and World Security Studies 1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - -Peace and World Security Studies 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - -Physical Education 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - -Sciences
        - -General 1978-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - -Astronomy 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
        - -Center for Theoretical Studies 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
        - -Coastal Marine Sciences 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
        - -Geology 1976-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - -Theatre 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - -Women's Studies 1976-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - -Alumni College 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - -Budget 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - -Budget 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - -Budget 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - -Center for Communication 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - -Computers 1978-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - -Conference of Consortium Presidents 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - -Credit Union 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - -Faculty Appointments 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - -Faculty Appointments 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - -Faculty Appointments 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - -Faculty Appointments 1978-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - -Five College Center 1978-1980, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - -Five College Fellowship 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - -Fred Friendly 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - -Grants and Proposals 1975-1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - -Grants and Proposals 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - -Grants and Proposals 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - -International Choral Festival 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - -International Programs 1976-1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - -Japanese Educational Administrator's Conference 1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - -Legislation and Legislators 1976-1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - -Libraries 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - -Libraries 1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - -Libraries 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - -Libraries 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - -Libraries 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - -Long-range Planning Committee 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - -Public School Partnership 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - -Management Development Program 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - -Massachusetts Review 1977-1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - -Microwave Study (Box 8)
      See Series XIV. Intercollegiate Associations-Five Colleges-Sciences-Astronomy
    - -"Mount Holyoke and the Five College Consortium" 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - -Museum Collaboration 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - -Racism 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - -Radio-WFCR 1975-1985, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - -Seminar/Reception for Administrative Officers and Staff 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - -Shofar Jewish News Magazine 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - -South Africa 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - -Third World Theatre Task Force (Box 9)
      See Series II. Academic Departments-Theatre-Black Theatre
    - -Transportation System 1975-1983 (Box 9)
      - -General 1975-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - -1979 Report 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - -WMBC 1976, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Seven Sisters
    - -General 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - -General 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - -General 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - -General 1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - -General 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - -Concentration Survey 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - -Development Conference 1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - -Seven College Research Project on Careers of Women Scholars 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - -Seven College Study
      - -General 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - -General 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - -Annual Report 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - -Annual Report 1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - -"Comparisons Between Pre-Med Students and Their..." 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - -"Comparisons Between Pre-Med Students and Their..." 1983 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - -NEH Grant Application 1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - -"Racial Comparisons for All Women in the Classes of..." 1983 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - -Random Sample Reports 1983 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - -Random Sample Reports 1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Society Organized Against Racism [SOAR] 1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Society Organized Against Racism 1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Society Organized Against Racism 1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Ten Universities Group 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Twelve-College Exchange 1976-1985 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    See also Series III. Acad Progs-Junior Year at Smith
  - Women's College Coalition 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    See also Series IV. Admin Issues-Legal Counsel, 1983
  - Women's College Coalition 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Women's College Coalition 1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Women's College Coalition 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Women's College Coalition 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- SERIES XV. NON-SMITH ORGANIZATIONS
  The files in this series are organized alphabetically by organization name, with a number of miscellaneous organizations also filed alphabetically, in the last few boxes.
  The material in this series documents the variety of national, regional and local organizations which had an impact on, and a relationship with, Smith College. Included are reports, newspaper clippings and correspondence with a number of academic, civic, corporate and nonprofit organizations. Organizations of particular interest are the Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts (AICUM), the Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), and state and federal government bodies.
  - Academy of American Poets 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academy for Educational Development 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alden Seminars Jan-May 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alden Seminars Jun-Dec 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alden Seminars 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Association of University Professors 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Association of University Women 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Council of Learned Societies 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Council on Education 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    See also Series XV. Non-Smith Organizations-Cooperative Institutional Research Program
  - American Council on Education 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Council on Education 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Council on Education-Commission on Higher Education 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - American Institute for Public Service 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Amnesty International 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Association of American College and University Programs in Italy 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Association of American Colleges 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Association of American Colleges 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Association of Colleges in New England 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts Jan-May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts Jun-Aug 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts Sep 1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts Oct-Dec 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts Jan 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts Feb-Apr 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts Jun-Dec 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Center for the Study of the Presidency 1977-1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Corporation 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - [Paul D.] Carre & Associates 1976, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Catalyst 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Catalyst 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Citizens' Talent Bank 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - College Board 1978-1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - College Venture Program 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Commission on College Retirement 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Commission for the Humanities 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Conference Board 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Conference on Higher Education Issues in Massachusetts-March 12, 1981 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Committee for the Concerns of Women in New England Colleges and U's 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Committee for the Concerns of Women in New England Colleges and U's 1977-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education Jan-Apr 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education May-Dec 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative Institutional Research Program 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cooperative Institutional Research Program 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Council for Advancement and Support of Education 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)